What did you just say?
All of House
Carter’s lands have fallen!
My lord… what is happening?
Could Severin actually be behind this?
No way.
How could a miner
wield that kind of power?
Severin!
Stop right there!
Severin,
What the hell have
you done to our family?
I just gave you
exactly what you asked for.
This can’t be happening.
A worthless failure like you
couldn’t
possibly have this kind of power.
Father, don’t fall for his lies!
It has to be a coincidence.
Exactly.
How could a miner
destroy an entire noble house?
If he were truly that powerful,
why would he waste his life digging in the dirt?
But our lands are
under attack right now!
If we don't stop it immediately...
House Carter will be completely erased
from Golantis within days!
Your new heir claims he knows
Steward Jeyn of the Sovereign Sanctum.
Go ask him for help.
This should be easy for him.
Right!
I’ll contact Steward Jeyn right now!
That's good.
May House Carter flourish forever...
under his leadership.
Severin!
And I’ll be
sure to bring you
a very special
gift for your wedding.
I look forward to it.
That stone… was it
really just a coincidence?
Father, he’s nothing
but a worthless miner!
But… he was far too confident.
Notify every branch
of the Sovereign Sanctum.
No one is permitted to
have any dealings with House Carter.
Disobey, and you will be executed.